[screaming sound]
Normal like
happy birthday [screaming sound] The
cake has melted and there will be havoc here
brother, I am still looking like that girl of theirs who
looks older than these parents,
okay guys, right
now there is a little photo session going on of these
boys, no matter
how much you cut the school girl, brother, she is
taking it very well.
Look at his face [Music]
This is my
brother, what birthday is this?  This is my third
flight to Goa.  Why is God
not letting me come to Goa?  In this condition I am at the
airport. Are you guys?  And hopefully I won't miss this
flight because it got
cut off, I was excited for Goa, but what is this, itni
ghasdi hai Goa jaane mein, this is
the first time I am training to Goa, this is the
third time
[laughs]
what happened brother?
Happy Birthday
[laughs]
Yes brother, I was watching him
walking around looking cool brother, what is this
camera
DG cam
brother, I got lost
brother, how is it?  Crazy woman, where are you brother?
Where from?
Brother, this was very good.
You have
n't seen the house, that's all I've seen so far.   Do
n't you know
where it is?  No, no one knows.
No, are you doing something?
Who picked it up?  I was asking when is she
coming.   Are you
doing something?
How did you become tall?
Brother, now the first thought that came to my mind was anger.
I will quickly take a bath and come back because
I have to create a lot of content brother.   After taking
rest,
hey, go to hell with rest.  Time toh main bahut aise hoti rahi baar phir
maine pata hai, I
played that song in the car, love it all
[singing voice] You Zindagi, this is what
you have taken,
how beautiful it is brother, and how dirty the room has been, he has taken such a
beautiful room,
what else do you expect, look at this, look
here, you have
taken the one with balcony, you are the birthday boy,
what a big one, I am taking this, run away and
show it to me [laughs]
brother, this is not matching,
today I will match the outfit with that only.   Mischievous mischievously,
I am ducking from below, which is not even coming on the
video,
guys
birthday girl
Goa is, I ca
n't see it,
I am just looking at the cow,
we came down at night, we sat down expecting it to be night,
brother, this is the beach, I can't see it, it must be the beach, there is a
drain on
that side, pluck mangoes, are you
making it for the first time?
Yes,
I have also come before you, this is
our first trip.
This is the first trip for all of us.  The rest of the people are still taking
bath.
And it is [ __ ] Goa yes
now it will be a spontaneous trip only.  I will suddenly
decide in one day.   It happened like this.
And the same thing happened.  And that too on my birthday.   It looks like a
festival now.   There is a
festival.  The day I was born is a
festival.
Cameraman, please focus here.  Focus Focus
Focus
Happy Birthday to Jayanti brother Happy Aku Jayanti
[laughter]
Happy Birthday
[screaming sound] I am
talking to you
[laughter]
Happy Birthday
Baika Listen listen listen
don't just wish him a happy birthday friend
in 2 minutes
brother he is saying that he is having some good times right now
so I should give him some credit
from God that he will have good
days in future then that will be my credit manifest
starting a manifestation
business so people whoever wants to get their manifest done get it done
I have put this in Paytm Paytm by
linking below [music] I will give only
UPI ID
Send QI [laughter] you leave the number from UPI
do it with the scanner brother guys
I didn't say someone tapped behind me like this so I
said you are saying wrong
ok someone tapped below means
I did it because small [laughter]
anyway
what's
wet is
not mine I have
one two three [screaming sound]
Happy New Year
Happy New Year they ran away
[laughter]  [screaming sound]
Listen, attention,
sir, I need a little secret topic, a little bit, what,
a beautiful flower for a
beautiful [laughs] beautiful lady,
yes brother, right now it's a
little contradictory, this
beautiful flower, beautiful
lady, is not matching, if you are done
with the eggs, move eggs [laughs]
then check
brother, I am 24, what should I say,
or which flower, beautiful flower for
a
beautiful [laughs] beautiful lady, it's not
matching, flower
brother, but it is that flower girl,
oh, this has to be done,
flower girl, flower
for flower,
flower girl, guys, hi guys, get ready
with us, earlier I was getting unready, now if I
go to the pool a little, I will get
ready,
or brother, tell me some story,
brother, do you know what, just
before he came, when our plan was almost
cancelled,
I was very sad that day, it had become so much that
brother, I don't
know what I was doing with work.  Is.  Two days
ago she said that she was going to Goa.  Then she says I am
not going.  Then she continues talking.
Wait, it's
story time.
I was with my friend
and I told them that brother, I don't know now,
tell me, is there no
God in Goa?  So he said
that there is a church.
She said that I will request him.
Lord, please call me to you.
If something happens this time, I will finally come
and
look, I don't know about them.  One has to
pray to God to indulge in homosexuality.
[laughs]
So in the meantime, one has to pray to God so much to touch water.
He is from Rajasthan, so am I?
Tell me water.
Water please.
Some people go crazy after seeing water.
Guys look the birthday girl is here.
Someone else is having a photo session.
Where did you say it from brother?
Hey brother, on top of that our neighbors are asking for sugar.
Guys, these guys are having a little photo session right now.
But [laughs] she is here
assistant
or she is just supporting.  Look at this pose of
our boy.   You are
watching cows and buffaloes over there, become a
cow and buffalo of Switzerland.  [laughter] These Are
the Flowers That I've Got.  When I
came down, all these were kept on the table.  I
made a lot of [music] reels with these.
[screaming sound] I look like a
child who looks older than these parents.
She is a child.
You are teasing the girls.  To the girls.
Come on, happy birthday Akanksha.
Well, this was in my vision board last year
that I want to earn 1.3 million and I want to
celebrate my 23rd birthday in Goa, so
I had put some photos of Goa beach in heart shape with 23 written on it in the vision board,
but it did not happen last year, so
I did it
this year.   There
is a couple channel on Insta called Midha and An.  Do you
know what the name is?
What is your name?  Look cute, what did you say?
Very cute.   I have my
own plan.
Its name is Butter Cake.
Hey cute, let's just go there,
they are cute with the cake [laughs]
Would you like to say something today,
what are your plans,
they are nice, this is it, it is
just missing, today you have to see this
bindi of mine that is coming
here [laughs]
natural bindi, she has brought our natural bindis,
look brother, she wants to go to the beach, she is taking them along,
look at her face,
how she is forcibly celebrating her birthday, she is
not letting me go to my house on my birthday.   She is
keeping us at home.
So celebrate my birthday.
We have to get through [laughter].
We have to go.
We have to pass by.   It has to
pass.
Who is the girl with all the dirty things?
Happy birthday to you.  Happy birthday to
you.
Stop, stop.  What were you showing?   Show
me that.  Our brother has become famous,
brother.  became mad.   Come
on guys.  This is like
these are small things about it.  [laughter] Gotta
give it.
Bro the guy Akanksha is so good looking.
[laughter] I
say, brother, what the [ __ ]?
I am looking good to people.
Listen, another photo.  [laughter]
Yeah, I'm a great friend of it.  Look,
we are the best thing in the same room.  [laughs]
Look, here's the reality of it, you might
find it beautiful too.  Please post this in the next redeemed post.
[laughter]
Best
what?
Completely opposite of ana.  [laughter]
But the three of us are very close.
Or Fisbaum?
Fisbb Fisbb
Fisbm?
Oh [laughs] if I had
stopped then right now guys are deciding whether
we should go out or not because I am
in pajamas what are you doing brother
this romantic whose wedding night is this here
[laughs] come on
friend he
says it is not necessary to go to the club then
when I applied glitter
what are you saying friend I have already applied glitter
and I am applying it in front of him
I am
applying glitter glitter and he is saying it is
not necessary to go to the club [laughs] I have stopped I have stopped
see I have applied too much on one of mine
[laughs] it is
not on both of mine because I
knew that I have a
glam outfit ready [laughs] I
also have it ready
oh tell me then I will cut it off, I am
asking in Vogue first that what
should I say and what should I not say [laughs] from
myself
from village area I have
285 followers brother [laughs] he is
taking sympathy he is taking sympathy the cake has
melted and is here.  There will be devastation
here now.  Brother, what clothes did this guy
show and she has come wearing them.  Four
outfits were shown.  She has come wearing it all shiny and bright.
Akshata, one brother, wait a minute.  Come
see.  Shut up, everyone, shut up.
Good.
Eat it all, eat it all.   Eat it
all.
Out.  A fast forward.   It feels a
little strange.  It tastes like medicine.   Will
you take it?
We fed cake to brother.  I have woken up from sleep.
What did these monks put in
this?
Oye makhane makhane, the same one with
spices.
Added spicy makhana and gave it.  My brother started eating.   Even if she
kills me, I will still
love her.  [laughs] He's torn about the hate
my fans get.
Tasted good with makhana.   It was
beautiful fun.   It looks
beautiful.   I will
break the drum.  [laughs]
Guys, we are here, all the Rajasthanis are
sitting here.  This is also their man.  Only this
one is left from Bargaon, they were
feeling left out and were telling Marwari
that you can join our gang.  I love
Nargarh?
I love will come.  [laughter] So get that
English out.   There was that
door outside.
Hey, don't get nervous seeing that camera.
I love Nawalgarh na.
Nawalgarh is mine.
Naralgarh, Naralgarh.
He comes to his in-laws' house.  No, what is maternal home
?   Don't know.
And then say that you will not do as you wish.   Do
n't do what you want.
And also say this, I will break it.  Break the dunga.
[laughs]
You don't even know this
Rajasthan Mercedes.   Do
n't know.
Mercedes Bro.  We call Mercedes [laughs]
Mercedes.
Let's go guys, this is the first time he has seen the beach today.  She has gone
mad.   I am feeling
scared that my goosebumps have come brother.
Come on, let's move ahead.   She would
tell me, show me the light here.  Yellow.
Seeing me she would say, brother, you must have gone.
I said I have seen Ju Bees.
[laughter] Go ahead.
Copy
this flower girl.  Hey, she took the light and went to
him.  Let us go.
Brother, this little girl came from behind.  Come once,
come from far away.  It seemed like Dumple Door was coming
brother.  By getting this hairstyle done.
Water Hey that's going up camera.  Look at
your by muscle memory.   Oh,
I forget.  If there is no complaint then these
people.
Your birthday is over now.
Now you can beat me now.  Guys, I thought they would take us out for a
little clubbing like this,
so I wore this outfit and came here at this
dhaba. Now we will eat Pani Puri. It's 2:00 in the night. Guys, I just came to know that
Pani Puri is closed today. The one behind, it's only
for the show.
What are you doing in Goa, brother?
This guy has come to
our temple today. Earlier,
this guy, look at my village.
Your village,
my village used to look like this. Now I will take you around my
village in my way. What a
happy birthday bro brother. God, it's
brother's birthday. Brother's
brother God, you have become a big man.   Isn't it
?
Its two million
guys look I'm so small.  What shall I
do?  She has come wearing heels.
No, we have brought this in your size.   Then you will have to
save the game.
Guys, we are on our way to our next location.
And the driver brother has run away with our luggage.
So we're chasing that right now.
Because all our clothes are in it.
If he doesn't come, we will have to roam around in these clothes every day.
I have been waiting in the car for so long.  Isn't it Akshata?  How much
weight has he made me wait?
Loose.
Yes.  We have been sitting here ready for a long time.
Post a screenshot of your gallery with this voice.   It's
my birthday.  Everyone is sitting after drinking drink.
What is it?  I'm not even in the entry.   Please
keep the Kalash here brother.
what is the matter?
Location number two is the candle.
So Lenny to Guys This is it's
those roles and nothing else.  misunderstand something